Louise Z. Young Photographs MS156
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Louise Z. Young Photographs
1947 -- 1965
1947 -- 1970
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Young, Louise Z.
MS156
1.0 Linear Feet 2 boxes
498 Digital Object(s)
Arrangement
This collection is organized in one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of photographic negatives and prints taken of events, places, and people around Tufts College from 1947-1965.
Biographical / Historical
Louise Z. Young was born in Corea, Maine in April, 1919. She began her career in photography when she took a position assisting a photographer in Bangor, Maine. Some of Young's best work came about as a result of her friendship with the American painter and poet Marsden Hartley. During World War II, she worked for The Bacharch Studio, where she was in charge of their darkroom. Following the war, Young and her partner, Jean Squttieri, opened their own studio in Beacon Hill, and later moved to Arlington, Massachusetts.
In the 1960s, Young worked with Bernice Abbott, printing the Parisian street scenes of French photographer Eugene Atget. She divided her time between her home in Arlington and her summer cottage in Corea, Maine, capturing the beauty and essence of the working village and its people. Young was a distinguished photographer for more than 65 years, until her death in July 2004.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
University history
- Negatives and Prints, 1947 -- 1970; MS156.001; 1.0 Linear Feet; 498 Digital Object(s)
  Scope and Contents
  This series consists of photographic negatives and prints taken of events, places, and people around Tufts College from 1947-1965
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Tufts-Architectural Shots Exteriors - Interiors, 1947; MS156.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
    - Hamilton Pool, 1947-08-14; MS156.001.001.00001.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Buildings
    - Entrance to Hamilton Pool, 1947-08-14; MS156.001.001.00001.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Doorways; Entrances
    - North corner view of Bray Mechanical Engineering Laboratory, 1947-08-14; MS156.001.001.00001.00003; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Buildings; Laboratories
    - Front view of Bray Mechanical Engineering Laboratory (1 of 2), 1947-08-14; MS156.001.001.00001.00004; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Front view of Bray Mechanical Engineering Laboratory (2 of 2), 1947-08-14; MS156.001.001.00001.00005; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Delta Tau Delta House, 1947-08-14; MS156.001.001.00001.00006; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Buildings; Fraternities; Greek letter societies; Delta Tau Delta
    - Alpha Tau Omega House, 1947-08-14; MS156.001.001.00001.00007; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Fraternities; Greek letter societies; Alpha Tau Omega
    - Chi Omega House, 1947-08-14; MS156.001.001.00001.00008; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Also exists as: UA136.002.DO.00492.
      Sororities; Greek letter societies; Chi Omega
    - Tufts Architectural Shots Exterior Interiors (9 of 10), 1947-08-14; MS156.001.001.00001.00009; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Tufts Architectural Shots Exterior Interiors (10 of 10), 1947-08-14; MS156.001.001.00001.00010; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Students kicking in water at Hamilton Pool, 1947-08-14; MS156.001.001.00001.00011; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Hamilton Pool; Students; negatives (photographic)
  - Tufts College - John Chiardi and Students, 1947; MS156.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
    - John Ciardi and students, 1947-10-22; MS156.001.001.00002.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Students; Poets; Ciardi, John
    - John Ciardi and students (2 of 2), 1947-10-22; MS156.001.001.00002.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Students --Poets; negatives (photographic); John Ciardi
  - Exteriors - Tufts College, 1948; MS156.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
    - View of Goddard Chapel from the Green, 1948-06-06; MS156.001.001.00003.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Exterior views
    - Eaton Hall covered in ivy, 1948-06-06; MS156.001.001.00003.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Buildings; Exterior views
    - Goddard Chapel and bell tower, 1948-06-06; MS156.001.001.00003.00003; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - View of Memorial Steps, 1948-06-06; MS156.001.001.00003.00004; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Memorial Steps --War Memorial Steps; negatives (photographic)
  - Jumbo - Tufts, 1949; MS156.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
    - Right angle view of Jumbo, 1949-05-12; MS156.001.001.00004.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Jumbo
    - Left angle view of Jumbo, with P.T. Barnum's desk in background, 1949-05-12; MS156.001.001.00004.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Jumbo and surrounding décor, 1949-05-12; MS156.001.001.00004.00003; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Also exists as: UA136.002.DO.02877.
  - View of Barnum Lounge, 1949; MS156.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
    - Barnum Lounge with students and Jumbo, 1949-05-12; MS156.001.001.00005.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Barnum Museum of Natural History --Barnum Hall; Students; negatives (photographic); Jumbo
  - Jumbo, 1882 -- 1949; MS156.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
    - Jumbo and Tom Thumb first see the approaching train (from print series), 1949-05-25; MS156.001.001.00006.00001; Unknown (Box 1)
      Also exists as: MS002.002.DO.00322.
    - Jumbo saving the clown elephant (from print series), 1949-05-25; MS156.001.001.00006.00002; Unknown (Box 1)
    - Jumbo struck by train (from print series), 1949-05-25; MS156.001.001.00006.00003; Unknown (Box 1)
    - Jumbo after the accident (from print series), 1949-05-25; MS156.001.001.00006.00004; Unknown (Box 1)
    - Jumbo in New York circus pamphlet, 1949-05-25; MS156.001.001.00006.00005; Unknown (Box 1)
      Also exists as: MS002.001.005.00002.00001.
    - Jumbo being fed by policeman, 1949-05-25; MS156.001.001.00006.00006; Unknown (Box 1)
      Also exists as: MS002.002.DO.00045.
    - Jumbo with riders, 1949-05-25; MS156.001.001.00006.00007; Unknown (Box 1)
    - Jumbo with riders (duplicate), 1949-05-25; MS156.001.001.00006.00008; Unknown (Box 1)
      Also exists as: MS156.001.001.00006.00007.
    - Advertising card featuring Jumbo's arrival (from Polaroid negative), MS156.001.001.00006.00009; Buek and Lindner (Box 1)
    - P.T. Barnum (from Polaroid negative), 1882; MS156.001.001.00006.00010; Wilde, Isaac (Box 1)
      Also exists as: MS002.002.DO.00041.
      P.T. Barnum; Wilde, Issac
  - Jumbo - for Jackson College, 1950; MS156.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
    - Jumbo figurine for Jackson College (1 of 3), 1950-01-05; MS156.001.001.00007.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Figurines; Jumbo
    - Jumbo figurine for Jackson College (2 of 3), 1950-01-05; MS156.001.001.00007.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Jumbo figurine for Jackson College (3 of 3), 1950-01-05; MS156.001.001.00007.00003; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
  - New Jackson Gym Exterior, 1950; MS156.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
    - Jackson Gym before Alumni Hall was built, 1950-05-12; MS156.001.001.00008.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
  - Exteriors of Tufts Campus for Grant Curtis, 1950; MS156.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
    - Long view of Ballou Hall and Goddard Chapel (View Book photograph for Grant Curtis), 1950-10-04; MS156.001.001.00009.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Side view of Ballou Hall and Goddard Chapel (View Book photograph for Grant Curtis), 1950-10-04; MS156.001.001.00009.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Path to Ballou Hall (View Book photograph for Grant Curtis), 1950-10-04; MS156.001.001.00009.00003; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Buildings; Exterior views; Trees
  - Exteriors - Bouve - Boston, 1951; MS156.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
    - Students outside entrance to Bouve-Boston School of Physical Education, 1951-10-09; MS156.001.001.00010.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Buildings; Exterior views; Students
    - Side angle view of Bouve-Boston School of Physical Education, 1951-10-09; MS156.001.001.00010.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Bouve-Boston School of Physical Education, 1951-10-09; MS156.001.001.00010.00003; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Buildings; Exterior views; Students; Trees
  - Dean Wessel and Pres. Carmichael, 1952; MS156.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
    - Dean Wessell and President Carmichael 'turning on switch', 1952-03-29; MS156.001.001.00011.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Wessell, Nils Yngve; Carmichael, Leonard
  - Chapel - Tufts, 1952; MS156.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
    - Goddard Chapel with scaffolding around bell tower, 1952-07-02; MS156.001.001.00012.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Buildings; Scaffolds; Exterior views
  - Ballou Hall, 1952; MS156.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
    - Students on lawn outside Ballou Hall, 1952-07-09; MS156.001.001.00013.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
  - Bray Mechanical Lab, 1952; MS156.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
    - View of Bray Mechanical Engineering Laboratory with people, 1952-08-07; MS156.001.001.00014.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Buildings; Laboratories; People
  - Jumbo Tradition and 3P's Officers, 1952; MS156.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
    - 3 P's officers putting pennies in Jumbo's trunk for good luck, 1952-10-22; MS156.001.001.00015.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Students; Traditions; Jumbo
    - 3 P's officers, 1952-10-22; MS156.001.001.00015.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Students; Pen, Paint, Pretzels
  - Tufts Commencement, 1953; MS156.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
    - George S. Eveleth receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1953-06-14; MS156.001.001.00016.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; Honorary degrees
    - Clarence E. Watkins receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1953-06-14; MS156.001.001.00016.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Bernt Balchen receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1953-06-14; MS156.001.001.00016.00003; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Robit Cutler receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1953-06-14; MS156.001.001.00016.00004; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Dean William DeVane receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1953-06-14; MS156.001.001.00016.00005; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Philip W. Johnson receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1953-06-14; MS156.001.001.00016.00006; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Harry Burden receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1953-06-14; MS156.001.001.00016.00007; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Sinclair Weeks receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1953-06-14; MS156.001.001.00016.00008; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Reverend John Nichol Mark receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1953-06-14; MS156.001.001.00016.00009; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Arnold Augustus Dirlam receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1953-06-14; MS156.001.001.00016.00010; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Arnold Augustus Dirlam shaking hands with Dean Wessell at Commencement, 1953-06-14; MS156.001.001.00016.00011; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Harry Burden shaking hands with Dean Wessell at Commencement, 1953-06-14; MS156.001.001.00016.00012; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Commencement speaker Dean DeVane, 1953-06-14; MS156.001.001.00016.00013; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement
    - Dean Jeffers with Jackson College students at Commencement, 1953-06-14; MS156.001.001.00016.00014; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; Students; Jackson College
    - Nils Yngve Wessell with marshals at Commencement, 1953-06-14; MS156.001.001.00016.00015; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Eveleth family at Commencement, 1953-06-14; MS156.001.001.00016.00016; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Three members of Eveleth family at Commencement, 1953-06-14; MS156.001.001.00016.00017; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Air Force ROTC at Commencement, 1953-06-14; MS156.001.001.00016.00018; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; Reserved Officers' Training Corps (Air Force)
    - Color Guard at Commencement, 1953-06-14; MS156.001.001.00016.00019; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Students receiving diplomas at Commencement, 1953-06-14; MS156.001.001.00016.00020; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; Students
  - Exteriors - Carmichael Hall, 1953; MS156.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
    - Full view of Carmichael Hall construction, 1953-10-17; MS156.001.001.00017.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Buildings; Exterior views; Construction
    - Elevated view of Carmichael Hall construction, 1953-10-17; MS156.001.001.00017.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
  - View Book Photographs for Grant Curtis, 1954; MS156.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
    - Teachers Council (View Book photograph for Grant Curtis), 1954-03-12; MS156.001.001.00018.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Faculty; Interior views; Meetings
    - Carmichael Hall (View Book photograph for Grant Curtis), 1954-03-12; MS156.001.001.00018.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Buildings; Exterior views; Dormitories
    - People walking down path from Ballou Hall (View Book photograph for Grant Curtis), 1954-03-12; MS156.001.001.00018.00003; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
  - Exteriors - New Tufts Buildings, 1954; MS156.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
    - Full view of new Jackson dorm construction, 1954-04-10; MS156.001.001.00019.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Buildings; Dormitories; Exterior views; Construction; Jackson College
    - Left angle view of Sweet Hall, 1954-04-10; MS156.001.001.00019.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Also exists as: UA021.001.010.00011.00001.
      Buildings; Exterior views; Reserved Officers' Training Corps (Air Force)
    - Full view of Carmichael Hall construction, 1954-04-10; MS156.001.001.00019.00003; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
  - Exteriors - Tufts, 1954; MS156.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
    - Alumni Gate, 1954-05-25; MS156.001.001.00020.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Gates
    - Front view of Eaton Memorial Library, 1954-05-25; MS156.001.001.00020.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Side view of Miner Hall, 1954-05-25; MS156.001.001.00020.00003; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Right angle view of Eaton Memorial Library with Goddard Chapel in background, 1954-05-25; MS156.001.001.00020.00004; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Alumni Gate with Goddard Chapel in background, 1954-05-25; MS156.001.001.00020.00005; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Trees
    - Couple walking toward Dearborn Gate, 1954-05-25; MS156.001.001.00020.00006; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Students
    - Students walking down path from Ballou Hall (1 of 2), 1954-05-25; MS156.001.001.00020.00007; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Students gathered outside entrance of Barnum Hall, 1954-05-25; MS156.001.001.00020.00008; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Students walking up path, taken through pillars of Ballou Hall, 1954-05-25; MS156.001.001.00020.00009; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Students; Columns (architectural elements)
    - Fischer Arcade, 1954-05-25; MS156.001.001.00020.00010; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Side angle view of Eaton Memorial Library, 1954-05-25; MS156.001.001.00020.00011; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Packard Hall covered in ivy, 1954-05-25; MS156.001.001.00020.00012; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Bendetson Hall, 1954-05-25; MS156.001.001.00020.00013; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Students in doorway of West Hall, 1954-05-25; MS156.001.001.00020.00014; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Buildings; Exterior views; Doorways; Students
    - Fischer Arcade seen from Memorial Steps, 1954-05-25; MS156.001.001.00020.00015; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Also exists as: UA136.002.DO.02008.
      Buildings; Students
    - Students in doorway of Packard Hall, 1954-05-25; MS156.001.001.00020.00016; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Bendetson Hall and West Hall, 1954-05-25; MS156.001.001.00020.00017; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Bowen Porch of Ballou Hall with Barnum Hall in background, 1954-05-25; MS156.001.001.00020.00018; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Goddard Chapel bell tower and Ballou Hall, 1954-05-25; MS156.001.001.00020.00019; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Front side view of Carmichael Hall, 1954-05-25; MS156.001.001.00020.00020; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Long side view of West Hall with Carmichael Hall in background, 1954-05-25; MS156.001.001.00020.00021; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
  - Repairs on Jumbo, 1954; MS156.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
    - Two men working on Jumbo restoration, 1954-05-26; MS156.001.001.00021.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Restoration and conservation; Jumbo
    - Four men working on Jumbo restoration, 1954-05-26; MS156.001.001.00021.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Also exists as: MS002.002.DO.00054.
  - Exterior - Ballou - Grant Curtis, 1954; MS156.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
    - Students walking down path from Ballou Hall (2 of 2) (View Book photograph for Grant Curtis), 1954-05-26; MS156.001.001.00022.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
  - Commencement - Tufts, 1954; MS156.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
    - Francis C. Gray receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1954-06-13; MS156.001.001.00023.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Christian Archibald Herter receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1954-06-13; MS156.001.001.00023.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Reverend Palfrey Perkins receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1954-06-13; MS156.001.001.00023.00003; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Henry T. Claus receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1954-06-13; MS156.001.001.00023.00004; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Senator John F. Kennedy receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1954-06-13; MS156.001.001.00023.00005; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Judge Charles E. Wyzanski receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1954-06-13; MS156.001.001.00023.00006; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Joseph P. Spang, Jr. receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1954-06-13; MS156.001.001.00023.00007; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Byron T. Atwood at Commencement, 1954-06-13; MS156.001.001.00023.00008; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Samuel Miller Brownell receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1954-06-13; MS156.001.001.00023.00009; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Brigadier General George R. Callender receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1954-06-13; MS156.001.001.00023.00010; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Unidentified speaker at Commencement (labeled as Morrison), 1954-06-13; MS156.001.001.00023.00011; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; Speeches
    - Christian Archibald Herter shaking hands with Dean Wessell at Commencement, 1954-06-13; MS156.001.001.00023.00012; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Commencement audience, 1954-06-13; MS156.001.001.00023.00013; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; Audiences
    - Tufts Trustees and honoraries in line at Commencement, 1954-06-13; MS156.001.001.00023.00014; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; Trustees; Honorary degrees
    - Jackson College students receiving diplomas at Commencement, 1954-06-13; MS156.001.001.00023.00015; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; Jackson College
    - Tufts Trustees and honoraries at Commencement with ROTC flag bearers, 1954-06-13; MS156.001.001.00023.00016; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; Trustees; Honoraries; Reserved Officers' Training Corps (Navy); Reserved Officers' Training Corps (Air Force)
    - Medical, Fletcher, Engineering, Graduate, and Jackson College students at Commencement, 1954-06-13; MS156.001.001.00023.00017; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Commencement crowd from above, 1954-06-13; MS156.001.001.00023.00018; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Commencement audience from right of stage, 1954-06-13; MS156.001.001.00023.00019; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Commencement audience and graduates from left of stage, 1954-06-13; MS156.001.001.00023.00020; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; Audiences; Students
    - Special Studies Jackson College students at Commencement, 1954-06-13; MS156.001.001.00023.00021; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Invocation at Commencement, 1954-06-13; MS156.001.001.00023.00022; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; Invocation; Flags
    - Jackson College students receiving diplomas at Commencement, 1954-06-13; MS156.001.001.00023.00023; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Senator John F. Kennedy and Dean Nils Wessell, 1954-06-13; MS156.001.001.00023.00024; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - NROTC at Commencement, 1954-06-13; MS156.001.001.00023.00025; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; Reserved Officers' Training Corps (Navy)
    - Honoraries at Commencement, 1954-06-13; MS156.001.001.00023.00026; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; Honoraries
  - Hodgdon and Carmichael Hall - Interiors, 1954; MS156.001.001.00024 (Box 1)
    - Students in Hodgdon Hall lounge, 1954-09-23; MS156.001.001.00024.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Buildings; Interior views; Lounges (sitting rooms)
    - Hodgdon Hall entrance and lounge, 1954-09-23; MS156.001.001.00024.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Buildings; Interior views
    - Professor talking with students in Carmichael Hall, 1954-09-23; MS156.001.001.00024.00003; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Buildings; Interior views; Students; Professors; Books
    - Students in Carmichael Hall lounge, 1954-09-23; MS156.001.001.00024.00004; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Buildings; Lounges (sitting rooms); Interior views; Students
    - Left angle view of students in Hodgdon Hall lounge, 1954-09-23; MS156.001.001.00024.00005; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Students studying in Carmichael Hall lounge, 1954-09-23; MS156.001.001.00024.00006; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Exterior view of Hodgdon Hall entrance, 1954-09-23; MS156.001.001.00024.00007; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Buildings; Exterior views; Entrances
    - Students in Metcalf Hall Lounge, 1954-09-23; MS156.001.001.00024.00008; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Alumnae Hall construction from road, 1954-09-23; MS156.001.001.00024.00009; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Buildings; Construction
    - Alumnae Hall construction from side, 1954-09-23; MS156.001.001.00024.00010; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Hodgdon Hall dining room viewed through window, 1954-09-23; MS156.001.001.00024.00011; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Buildings; Dinners and Dining; Interior views; Students
    - Cohen Arts Center construction, side view, 1954-09-23; MS156.001.001.00024.00012; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Cohen Arts Center construction, rear view, 1954-09-23; MS156.001.001.00024.00013; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Football game from sideline, 1954-09-23; MS156.001.001.00024.00014; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Athetics; Football; Students
    - Sweet Hall entrance with students, 1954-09-23; MS156.001.001.00024.00015; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Buildings; Exterior views; Students; Reserved Officers' Training Corps
    - Students in front of Sweet Hall, 1954-09-23; MS156.001.001.00024.00016; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Buildings; Exterior views; Students; Entrances; Reserved Officers' Training Corps
    - Right angle view of Hodgdon Hall, 1954-09-23; MS156.001.001.00024.00017; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Also exists as: UA136.002.DO.01673.
    - Posner Hall, 1954-09-23; MS156.001.001.00024.00018; Duette Photographers (Box 1)